## Tyler Poor

## Cybersecurity

#### Contact

### Summary

7000 Bowen Corner Avenue, Apt. 7308, Hanahan, SC, 29410 843-735-9163 mtpoor05@gmail.com Cybersecurity driven individual with a passion for continual learning. Deep passion in ethical hacking and penetration testing. Driven, focused, and willing to set goals and reach them. In-depth experience in System Administration, System Security, Security Policies, Threat Analyzing, and Network Penetration Testing.

#### Education

Charleston Southern University North Charleston, SC Strong curriculum in Information Security and Computer Science.

**GPA**: 3.7

Coursework Includes: Network
Penetration Testing, Applied
Networking, Cyber Defense, Cyber
Analytics, Cyber Forensics, Studies
in Cyber Security, Scripting
Languages, OO Programming,
Procedural Programming.

## Certifications and Courses

CompTIA Security+ E-Learning Security eJPT

TCM Security's Practical Ethical
Hacking
TCM Security's Windows Privilege
Escalation
TCM Security's OSINT

#### **Experience**

May 2021 - Present

Cybersecurity Intern • with a focus in penetration testing, vulnerability management, Windows configuration and patching, network device configuration, security policy writing and implementation, social engineering, and exploit development • UEC Electronics

- Successfully hacked our company within two days and took control of the domain controller.
- Wrote and implemented Event Monitoring Policy, Incident Investigation Process, Vulnerability Management Policy, USB Policy, New Device Hardening Process
- Created, implemented, and monitored security controls to become CMMC and NIST SP 800-171 compliant.
- Closed over 100,000 vulnerabilities on our network in 6 months.
- Upgraded our asset inventory of over 500 machines.
- Implemented next-gen antivirus, RMM Patching service, installed Palo Alto 440 firewall, and built a VPN tunnel from our acquisition company to UEC Electronics.
- Enabled business processes by handling workflow tickets in an efficient and professional manner.
- Ran successful phishing campaigns raising security awareness.
- Implemented disk encryption on all endpoints and servers.
- Successfully remediated all vulnerabilities found during the penetration test within a month.
- Assisted in legacy device network segmentation.
- Conducted multiple risk assessments on software and hardware devices

May 2020 – August 2020

Instructor Assistant • Facilitated an energetic and beneficial learning environment to teach new students concepts in Python, Java, JavaScript, and C++ • Nucamp Coding

October 2020 - Present

Online Business Owner • Running a successful online marketing company that focuses on running social media ads to develop leads. Meet with business owners periodically to assess marketing needs. • Upscale Marketing

#### **Key Skills**

# Penetration Testing Vulnerability Management System Administration Desktop Servicing Networking Policy Writing Teamwork Soft Skills and Presenting Active Directory Exploitation Linux Hardening

#### Communication

Gave presentation on a successful penetration test and steps toward remediation to the President and IT Security Directory of UEC Electronic

Gave presentation to all employee body on the importance of information security and watching for insider threats within the workplace.

#### Links

https://www.linkedin.com/in/tylerpoor-929584193/

https://tylerpoor05.wixsite.com/mysite

#### **Technical Experience**

Nmap, Palo Alto Firewalls, Burp Suite, CrowdStrike Falcon, NinjaOne, Metasploit, Nikto, Nessus, Kali Linux, Python, Windows Administration, Server Administration, Incident Response, Network Debugging, IT Troubleshooting, Active Directory Penetration Testing, WebApp Penetration Testing, Ubuntu, Threat Hunting/Analyst, Networking, Wireshark, HackTheBox, TryHackMe, Recon-ng, SMB Exploitation, Hashcat, John, Aircrack-ng, Reaver, Social Engineering Toolkit, SQLmap, Responder, Impacket Toolkit, MiTM Attacks, Mimikatz, Bloodhound, PowerView, Empire, Powersploit, WinPEAS, SMBEnum, DNSEnum, theHarvester, Maltego, PSExec,

#### References

Jon Dorsey, Thomas Hope, Eric Stone